let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How many pressure gauges are in regulator?",
    immg: "img1",
    answer: "Two pressure gauges",
    options: [
      "One pressure gauge",
      "Two pressure gauges",
      "Three pressure gauges",
      "Four pressure gauges"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What procedure is followed to connect gas regulator to cylinder in gas welder?",
    immg: "img2",
    answer: "Open and close valve for few seconds",
    options: [
      "Open and close valve for few seconds",
      "Open the valve for a longer period",
      "No need to open the valve before connection",
      "Open the valve for a few minutes of time"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which type of welding uses a non-ferrous filler with melting point above 450Â°C than base metal?",
    immg: "img3",
    answer: "Brazing",
    options: [
      "Brazing",
      "Soldering",
      "Arc welding",
      "Gas welding"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which welding process enables to weld dissimilar metals?",
    immg: "img4",
    answer: "Brazing",
    options: [
      "Brazing",
      "Seam welding",
      "Spot welding",
      "MIG welding"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is included the angle for a double bevel butt joint?",
    immg: "img5",
    answer: "45o",
    options: [
      "45o",
      "35o",
      "60o",
      "20o"
    ]
  },
  
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "What is the colour of calcium carbide?",
      immg: "img6",
      answer: "Dark - Grey",
      options: [
        "Dark - Red",
        "Dark - Grey",
        "Dark - Blue",
        "Dark - Yellow"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "What is the symbol of oxygen?",
      immg: "img7",
      answer: "O2",
      options: [
        "O2",
        "C2",
        "H2O",
        "C2H2"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which gas dissolves in acetone liquid?",
      immg: "img8",
      answer: "Acetylene",
      options: [
        "Oxygen",
        "Nitrogen",
        "Hydrogen",
        "Acetylene"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which gas supports to combustion of fuels?",
      immg: "img9",
      answer: "Oxygen",
      options: [
        "Oxygen",
        "Acetylene",
        "Hydrogen",
        "Carbon di oxide"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which document lists all the essential characteristics for performing a weld?",
      immg: "img10",
      answer: "Weld procedure specification",
      options: [
        "Weld procedure specification",
        "Welder performance qualification",
        "Welding procedure qualification",
        "Welding procedure specification"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "What is the colour of acetylene cylinder?",
      immg: "img11",
      answer: "Maroon",
      options: [
        "Blue",
        "Black",
        "Yellow",
        "Maroon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "What is the name of the cylinder shown in the figure?",
      immg: "img12",
      answer: "Oxygen",
      options: [
        "Oxygen",
        "Acetylene",
        "Argon gas",
        "Carbon-di-oxide"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "What is the name of the pressure system shown in figure?",
      immg: "img13",
      answer: "High",
      options: [
        "Low",
        "High",
        "Normal",
        "Medium"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "What is the name of the pressure system shown in figure?",
      immg: "img14",
      answer: "Low",
      options: [
        "Low",
        "High",
        "Normal",
        "Medium"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "What is the welding technique shown in the figure?",
      immg: "img15",
      answer: "Leftward",
      options: [
        "Leftward",
        "Rightward",
        "Backward",
        "Upto downward"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "What is the angle of blowpipe in leftward technique?",
      immg: "img16",
      answer: "60o-70o",
      options: [
        "30o-40o",
        "50o-60o",
        "60o-70o",
        "80o-90o"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "What is name of the brazing shown in figure?",
      immg: "img17",
      answer: "Furnace",
      options: [
        "Dip brazing",
        "Torch",
        "Furnace",
        "Induction"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "Which welding defects have pin holes formed on the surface?",
      immg: "img18",
      answer: "Porosity",
      options: [
        "Spatter",
        "Porosity",
        "Blow holes",
        "Burn through"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "What is the symbol of flat or down hand position?",
      immg: "img19",
      answer: "PA",
      options: [
        "PA",
        "PC",
        "PB",
        "PD"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "What is the effect of arc blow?",
      immg: "img20",
      answer: "Poor fusion",
      options: [
        "Less spatters",
        "Poor fusion",
        "Good weld",
        "Good penetration"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 21,
      question: "What is defect in welded job to change its size and shape permanently?",
      immg: "img21",
      answer: "Distortion",
      options: [
        "Arc blow",
        "Spatters",
        "Distortion",
        "Incomplete"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 22,
      question: "What is the letter H indicating the electrode coding?",
      immg: "img22",
      answer: "Hydrogen controlled",
      options: [
        "Hydrogen controlled",
        "Electrode efficiency",
        "Current condition",
        "Radio graphic quality"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 23,
      question: "What is the use of calcium carbide?",
      immg: "img23",
      answer: "Produces acetylene gas",
      options: [
        "Produces acetylene gas",
        "Produces oxygen gas",
        "Produces nitrogen gas",
        "Produces hydrogen gas"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 24,
      question: "What is the percentage of calcium in calcium carbide?",
      immg: "img24",
      answer: "62.5%",
      options: [
        "50.2%",
        "57.3%",
        "62.5%",
        "75.3%"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 25,
      question: "What is the colour of liquid oxygen?",
      immg: "img25",
      answer: "Pale blue",
      options: [
        "Pale blue",
        "Dark blue",
        "Pale yellow",
        "Dark yellow"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 26,
      question: "At which temperature the liquid oxygen becomes solid?",
      immg: "img26",
      answer: "-218.4oC",
      options: [
        "-200oC",
        "-205oC",
        "-218.4oC",
        "-325.3oC"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 27,
      question: "What is percentage of oxygen in atmosphere?",
      immg: "img27",
      answer: "21%",
      options: [
        "21%",
        "33%",
        "45%",
        "52%"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 28,
      question: "What is the colour of welding oxygen cylinder?",
      immg: "img28",
      answer: "Black",
      options: [
        "Red",
        "Blue",
        "Black",
        "Maroon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 29,
      question: "Which cylinder is fitted with safety fuse plug?",
      immg: "img29",
      answer: "Acetylene",
      options: [
        "Oxygen",
        "Argon",
        "Acetylene",
        "Carbon-di-oxide"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 30,
      question: "What is the capacity of welding an oxygen cylinder?",
      immg: "img30",
      answer: "7m3",
      options: [
        "5m3",
        "7m3",
        "10m3",
        "15m3"
      ]
    }
  
  
    {
      numb: 31,
      question: "Which is the name of the welding technique shown in the figure?",
      immg: "img31",
      answer: "Rightward",
      options: [
        "Leftward",
        "Rightward",
        "Forehand",
        "Downward"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 32,
      question: "Which type of blowpipe is used in the high pressure system?",
      immg: "img32",
      answer: "Non injector",
      options: [
        "Needle",
        "Injector",
        "Purifier",
        "Non injector"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 33,
      question: "In which welding technique, the welding starts at the right hand edge and moves towards the left?",
      immg: "img33",
      answer: "Leftward",
      options: [
        "Leftward",
        "Rightward",
        "Backward",
        "Up and Downward"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 34,
      question: "What is the full form of CCMS?",
      immg: "img34",
      answer: "Copper Coated Mild Steel",
      options: [
        "Copper Coated Mild Steel",
        "Carbon Coated Mild Steel",
        "Calcium Coated Mild Steel",
        "Chromium Coated Mild Steel"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 35,
      question: "What is the function of flux in Oxy-acetylene gas welding?",
      immg: "img35",
      answer: "Prevents oxidation",
      options: [
        "Prevents oxidation",
        "Combustion of metal",
        "Strengthens filler rod",
        "Strengthens electrode"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 36,
      question: "What is the name of the brazing shown in the figure?",
      immg: "img36",
      answer: "Torch brazing",
      options: [
        "Dip brazing",
        "Torch brazing",
        "Furnace brazing",
        "Induction brazing"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 37,
      question: "What is the name of the part marked as X shown in the figure?",
      immg: "img37",
      answer: "Soldering iron",
      options: [
        "Base metal",
        "Copper tip",
        "Soldering iron",
        "Soldered seam"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 38,
      question: "What is the name of the defect marked as X shown in the figure?",
      immg: "img38",
      answer: "Blow holes",
      options: [
        "Cracks",
        "Porosity",
        "Blow holes",
        "Burn through"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 39,
      question: "What is the S.I unit of heat?",
      immg: "img39",
      answer: "Joule",
      options: [
        "Calorie",
        "Joule",
        "Centigrade heat unit",
        "British thermal unit"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 40,
      question: "What is the value for specific heat of water?",
      immg: "img40",
      answer: "1",
      options: [
        "4",
        "3",
        "2",
        "1"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 41,
      question: "What is the boiling point of water?",
      immg: "img41",
      answer: "100oC",
      options: [
        "0oC",
        "32oC",
        "100oC",
        "212oC"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 42,
      question: "Which is the unit of current?",
      immg: "img42",
      answer: "Ampere",
      options: [
        "Ampere",
        "Volt",
        "Ohm",
        "Watt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 43,
      question: "What is the flow of electrons in any conductor?",
      immg: "img43",
      answer: "Current",
      options: [
        "Voltage",
        "Current",
        "Resistance",
        "Power"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 44,
      question: "What is the side of a square whose area is 625mm2?",
      immg: "img44",
      answer: "25 mm",
      options: [
        "15 mm",
        "20 mm",
        "25 mm",
        "30 mm"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 45,
      question: "Identify the name of tool?",
      immg: "img45",
      answer: "Try square",
      options: [
        "Try square",
        "Surface gauge",
        "Steel rule",
        "Feeler gauge"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 46,
      question: "Identify the name of tool?",
      immg: "img46",
      answer: "Ball pein hammer",
      options: [
        "Ball pein hammer",
        "Cross pein hammer",
        "Straight pein hammer",
        "Sledge hammer"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 47,
      question: "Identify the name of tool?",
      immg: "img47",
      answer: "Cutting plier",
      options: [
        "Hawk-billed shear",
        "Aviation shear",
        "Cutting plier",
        "Double cutting shear"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 48,
      question: "Identify the name of tool?",
      immg: "img48",
      answer: "Mallet",
      options: [
        "Ball pein hammer",
        "Mallet",
        "Cross pein hammer",
        "Staright pein hammer"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 49,
      question: "Identify the name of tool?",
      immg: "img49",
      answer: "Open end spanner",
      options: [
        "Open end spanner",
        "Ring spanner",
        "Combination spanner",
        "Adjustable spanner"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 50,
      question: "Which dimension correctly marked in the circle as per standard?",
      immg: "img50",
      answer: "A2",
      options: [
        "A1",
        "A2",
        "A3",
        "A4"
      ]
    }
  
  
];
